(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T21:14:54.900835",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
プロデューサー！！！
Producer!!!
どうしたんですか、ラプラスさん
What's the matter, La+-san?
次の生誕ライブ、なんにもやることないんですけど！！
For my next birthday live, I have nothing left to do!!
毎年いろいろやってきたけど…
I've done so many things every year, but...
去年は、ミームやりすぎて、ミームキャラになっちゃったし、どうしよう？
last year I went too hard on memes and became a meme character! What should I do?!
デビュー当時のアイドルらしさは もう見る影もないですからね
There's hardly any trace left of the idol charm you had at your debut, after all.
吾輩はどうやっていけば良いんだー
How am I supposed to handle this?!
勝手にTier表とか作っちゃいましたし...
I went ahead and made a Tier List without asking...
それだ!!!! ほら、吾輩、お姉さん大好きでしょ？
That's it! Look, I love older sisters, right?
ホロライブのお姉さんを大集合させよう！お姉さんライブだ！！！
Let's gather all the Hololive big sisters! It'll be a Big Sister Live!
大丈夫だよ！当てはある！！！吾輩に任せとけ！
It'll be fine! I have a plan! Leave it to me!
それはちゃんとラプラスさんのライブとして成立するんですか？
Will that actually work out as a proper Laplus-san live show?
そこは･･･なんかいい感じにやるんだよ！
Well... I'll figure that out nicely somehow!
ていうか、吾輩のこと好きなファンならさ、やっぱり、吾輩が好きなことしてるところ、楽しく見てくれるんじゃない！？
I mean, fans who like me would enjoy watching me do what I love, wouldn't they?!
限度があるんじゃないですか？
Isn't there a limit to that?
とにかくやるって決めたらやるの！いくぞー！！！
Once I decide to do it, I do it! Here I go!
ノエルさん！
Noel-san!
どうしたの？ラブちゃん？
What's wrong, Lap-chan?
実はい、もうすぐ吾輩の生誕ライブがあるんですけど、よかったらノエルさんにも出てほしいなって...
Actually, my birthday live is coming up soon, and I was hoping you'd join too, Noel-san...
えー！ラブちゃん誘ってくれるの！？嬉しい！もちろんだよ！
Eh?! You're inviting me, Lap-chan?! I'm so happy! Of course!
よーし！団長、歌とダンス頑張っちゃおうかな！先輩として、かっこいいところ見せちゃうよー！！！
All right! Danchou will give her all in singing and dancing! As your senior, I'll show off my cool side!
あ、いや...歌は吾輩がやるんで...ね？ほら、これ持って！
Ah, no... I'll be doing the singing... right? Here, hold this!
え、なにに？どういうこと？これってうちわ？
Huh, what? What do you mean? Is this an Uchiwa fan?
さて、あとは何を歌うかですね...
Well then, all that's left is deciding what to sing...
一曲目はね、きっとノエルさんもしあわせ...喜んでくれるはず！
For the first song, I'm sure Noel-san will be happy too!
え！？団長が！？
Eh?! Danchou?!
去年からノエルさんの影響からか吾輩のファン層が広がって、こういう曲が喜んでもらえるかなー！って思って！
Since last year, maybe thanks to your influence, my fanbase expanded, so I thought a song like this would make everyone happy!
えー！！期待しちゃうけど...いいのおお！？
Ehhh!! Now I'm getting my hopes up... Is it really okay?!
良いですよー！一曲目盛り上がっていきましょうおー！
It's totally fine! Let's get hyped up for song number one!
存外見掛け倒しな 虚勢張ってるロマンス
A romance that's surprisingly all show and bluff,
組み替えちまって遺伝子
Recombining genes,
トゥケトゥケな電波に乗った感情論
An emotional argument riding on electro waves,
僕のアピール見逃さないでよ
Don't miss my appeal!
嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ
No, no, no, no!
人間なんて誰だって こういうのが好きなんだって
Everyone's human, after all, and they all love this stuff,
一人善がりオーガズムネイション 溢れてドヴァドヴァ
A self-satisfied orgasm-nation, overflowing uncontrollably!
年季入りなあざとさ 「好き」の塗りたくり
Seasoned slyness, plastered with "I love yous,"
決めるぜ僕のラブ・ヴァリガルマンダ！
Time to land my Love Varigarmanda!
膨らんじゃった やばおぴ加減
It swelled up, it's getting crazy,
最高潮ののをくれてやる
I'll give you the ultimate climax!
好きって言葉で宥めて 迎え撃つから
Soothe me with "I love you" and I'll meet you head-on,
君のアイデンティティティティティーン
Your identity-ty-ty-ty-teen!
侮らないで 夢みがちボーイ
Don't underestimate this dreamy boy,
意外とありなんだって気づいて
Realize that it's surprisingly acceptable,
妄想フラストレーション 毛頭暴走
Delusional frustration, out-of-control impulse,
止まらないギガンテック
Unstoppable Gigantic,
よそ見厳禁 見ててててね？
No looking away, keep watching, okay?
ラブちゃん最高ー！
Lap-chan, you're the best!
もっと輝いてー！
Shine even brighter!
可愛いぞー！
You're so cute!
3 2 1 で目覚めて
Wake up on 3, 2, 1,
恋に落ちたりなんかして
Fall in love or something,
わし掴んでシークレット
Grab ahold of it secretly,
あ、なんだやっぱり単純で
Ah, see? It really is simple!
僕にとって僕が 揺るぎない絶対王政
For me, I am an unwavering absolute monarchy,
だからね君だって僕が大好きでしょ？
So you must love me too, right?
見せたげる聖域 僕だけの領域
I'll show you my sanctuary, my exclusive domain,
息遣いドキドキ 優しくしてばか
Breathing fast, heart pounding, be gentle, dummy!
山盛りなあいうえおんちゅ
A mountain load of love and kisses,
ワンタッチでリッチな
With one touch, a rich,
ドロリドロリと心に溶かして
Melting thickly into your heart,
愛 need you 誤算過ぎた僕のエラートラップ
I need you! My error trap was a huge miscalculation,
ここは限界突破ラブゲーム
This is a limit-breaking love game,
加速しちゃって
Accelerating faster and faster!
やばおぴ加減最高潮ののを
The ultimate level of craziness,
見せてやれ
Show it off!
駆け引き上手な僕がルール
Master of tactics, I make the rules,
狙い撃ち君をプラマイプラスで
Sniping you, turning minus into plus,
引き返せない二人だけの秘密
A point-of-no-return secret just for the two of us,
意外とありかもなんて
Thinking it might actually be okay,
気づいた？罪作りラブポーション
Did you notice? A sinful love potion,
一切合切とめどないギガンテック
Absolutely endless Gigantic,
目移りなんて許さないね？
Looking at anyone else is forbidden, okay?
「おちんちん」はギガンテックO.T.Nの略称であり、
"Ochinchin" is an abbreviation of Gigantic O.T.N,
主に突起物であるので扱われており、男女兼用である。
which mainly refers to a protrusion and is unisex.
最近では... あっ、違う！
Lately... Ah, wait, no!
吾輩の生誕ライブに乗っていこう！とりあえず吾輩の配信を...最後まで見続けてくれると思って...
Let me get into the spirit of my birthday live! I thought you'd keep watching my stream until the end...
あっ！あーっ！あーっ！
Ah! Ahhh! Ahhh!
全然... 全くの別物になっちゃった！違う違う違う！とりあえず一曲目、全部忘れて聴いてくれー！
This turned into... a totally different thing! No no no! For now, forget all of this for the first song and listen!
膨らんじゃった やばおぴ加減
It swelled up, it's getting crazy,
最高潮ののを与えてやる
I'll give you the ultimate climax!
好きって言葉で宥めて
Soothe me with "I love you,"
迎え撃つから 君のアイデンティティティティティーン
And I'll meet your identity-ty-ty-ty-teen head-on!
侮らないで 夢みがちボーイ
Don't underestimate this dreamy boy,
意外とありなんだって気づいて
Realize that it's surprisingly acceptable,
妄想フラストレーション 毛頭暴走
Delusional frustration, out-of-control impulse,
止まらないギガンテック
Unstoppable Gigantic,
指切り拳万 嘘ついたら 40発撃つ 乱れ撃ち
Pinky swear, if you lie, 40 random shots fired!
ラプくんの時代が来た！
Lap-kun's era has finally arrived!
ショタかわちーよ！ラプくん、輝いてる！
The shota is so cute! Lap-kun, you're shining!
最後まで輝いてー！
Keep shining until the very end!
さすがに先輩をファン扱いするのはどうかと思いますよ？
Don't you think treating your senior like a fan is a bit much?
いや、ノエルさんはファンでしょ！ファンっていうか、ママになろうとしてる人...？
No, Noel-san is definitely a fan! Or rather, someone trying to be my mom...?
とにかく、めっちゃ盛り上がってましたやん！
Anyway, she was super hyped up, wasn't she?!
てかてか、お姉さんといえば、ホロライブって学校みたいじゃない？
I mean, speaking of big sisters, isn't Hololive basically like a school?
学校？
A school?
学校のみんなのアイドル...そらさん
Everyone's school idol... Sora-san.
隣のクラスの留学生...キアラさん
The exchange student in the class next door... Kiara-san.
凛とした清楚な先輩...AZKiさん
The dignified and refined senior... AZKi-san.
部活の先輩お姉さま...ネリッサ
The big sister senior from the club... Nerissa.
クールビューティーな先生...クロニー
The cool beauty teacher... Kronii.
そして、同じクラスにいる、うるさい幼馴染の同級生...いろは
And the noisy childhood friend in the same class... Iroha.
そうだ！これをライブでやれば、盛り上がること間違いなし！そうと決まれば早速突撃だー！
That's it! If I do this at the live, it'll definitely be a hit! Now that it's set, time to charge in!
次から次へとすごい行動力だ...
Moving on to the next thing so fast... What incredible drive...
いろはー！
Iroha~!
ん？なんの用でござるか？
Hmm? What is it, de gozaru?
ライブでやりたい曲あるんだけど、見ててくんない？
I have a song I want to perform at the live, can you watch it for me?
？？？見る？？？どういうことでござる？
??? Watch??? What do you mean, de gozaru?
そう！見るだけ！やっぱり幼馴染と言えば、いつでも見守ってくれる存在だからね...
Yeah! Just watch! After all, when you think of childhood friends, they're the ones who always watch over you...
ただそこにいるだけで良い、そばにいてくれるだけ、その温かさが沁みるんだ
Just being there is enough. Just staying by my side, that warmth really touches me.
え...なんか気持ちわるいでござる...
Gross... that's kind of creepy, de gozaru...
いいからいいから！さ！行くぞー！
It's fine, it's fine! Come on, let's go!
え？
Huh?
なこれ？
What's this?
な、なこれ？
Wh-what is this?
なこれ？
What's this?
の、の、なこれ？
Wh-wh-what's this?
え？なに？
Huh? What?
な、なに...？
Wh-what...?
ラプラスちゃん...？
Laplus-chan...?
お...？
Oh...?
おー！
Ooh!
え、え？えぇ？
Huh, what? Ehhh?
隣のクラスに最近ちょっと気になっているあのコ
That kid in the class next door I've been interested in lately,
ポニーテールのきみ...抜き...抜き...スマイル
You with the ponytail... cheeky... cheeky... smile!
いやいやいやいや別に好きとかそんなんじゃないよ
No, no, no, no, it's not like I like them or anything!
ただちょっとちょっとちょっと目で追いかけているだけだってば
I'm just following them with my eyes a little bit, I tell you!
ってすでに結構メロメロなんだって！
You're already totally head over heels!
勉強も全然頭に入ってこなくてヤバい！
I can't even focus on studying at all, this is bad!
さっき君に一言かけられただけで
Just because they spoke a single word to you earlier!
こんな気持ち初めての事でもねえ声かけてくれた気味の事直接の事と言ってきます
Feelings like this aren't even the first time, but since they talked to me I'll tell them directly!
怖〜〜〜いって！
That's so scaaary!
やめ...やめて...！
St-stop it...!
や〜っ、可愛〜い！
Yay, so cute~!
やめろっつんだろ！
I told you to stop!
ピピピッと飛ばすぜDTE
Beep beep, let's blow past DTE!
乗ってくぜっくの波...大大混雑
Riding the wave of excitement... major traffic jam!
なかなかドッキリ...君の君の君の君の...
Quite a surprise... your, your, your, your...
どっ君！
Thump!
見せて見せて見せてちゃんと見せて見せてABCD...
Show me, show me, show me, properly show me ABCD...
我慢っっっっっっっと...我慢できない！
Endure... I can't hold back!
下下...青春期...でそこ...もう！
Lower... adolescence... over there... jeez!
おっ、画質が上がったか？え？
Oh, did the resolution just go up? Huh?
3学年の貴神の乙女で白磁の...先輩！
The noble maiden of the 3rd year... Senior!
そんなに近くに近付けられたらもうドキドキたまんなくて！
If you get that close to me, my heart won't stop pounding!
チラ見して...最高見ちゃった最高見ちゃった
Glancing over... I saw the best, I saw the best!
どこ見てんのよ！
Where are you looking?!
英検...漢字...
Eiken... Kanji...
生姜焼き...先輩に贈る好物...
Ginger pork... senior's favorite dish...
リアル自重しだした...止められない...
Really starting to restrain myself... can't stop it...
本能の俺の...シー、シークレット...！
Of my instincts... S-Secret...!
おい！
Hey!
どっちを選ぶのー！
Which one do you choose?!
えっ？
Huh?
イマジナリーお姉さんと...
Between imaginary big sisters and...
どっちも嫌だろ！
Both sound terrible!
すみませんでしたー！
I'm so sorry!
ピピピッと飛ばすぜDTE...抜け上がれ！
Beep beep, let's blow past DTE... rise up!
ダメダメダメダメ...クラッと
No, no, no, no... feeling dizzy!
俺の俺の俺の俺の...ふぁっきん
Mine, mine, mine, mine... freakin'!
濃くて濃くて...濃くて
Deep, deep... deep!
声上げてABCD...
Raise your voice ABCD...
だってひで...危険...ピッピッ
But awful... dangerous... beep beep!
下下...年頃...でそこそこそこ
Lower... that age... right there, there, there!
ちょっとだけ...ちょっとだけ...ちょっとだけ...ほら！
Just a little... just a little... just a little... look!
ちょっと男子！
Hey, boys!
ちょっとだけ...ちょっとだけ見せて...ちょっとだけ...LINEやってる？
Just a little... show me just a little... just a little... Do you use LINE?
えろっ！
Pervert!
何？何？何？
What? What? What?
合わせ...合わせ...いいよ...分かって...
Together... together... okay... understood...
やって...ねぇ...ねぇ...
Do it... hey... hey...
あーーーーーっ！
AAAAAHHH!
手を合わせてください！はい、みんなで！
Put your hands together! Come on, everyone!
いただきます！
Itadakimasu!
行きます！
Here we go!
さようなら 乙女心 咲かせて 咲く 先生 皆さん
Goodbye, blooming maiden heart! Teacher, everyone,
おピンピンで！
stay healthy!
元気すぎるだろ…
She's way too energetic...
ピンチ飛ばしまくり 青春 青春 乗ってくぜ どこまでも 大・大・大咲花
Blowing past crises, youth, youth! Riding it wherever, blooming big, big, big!
こわい…
Scary...
君の 君の 君の 君の…
Your, your, your, your...
見せて 見せて もっと見せて 見せて 見せて ちゃんと見せて 見せて 見せて ABCDEFG！
Show me, show me, show me more! Show me, show me, show me properly! ABCDEFG!
我慢 ちょっと我慢 やっぱ我慢できない しった しった し 春期で そっと ころころ…
Endure, endure a bit, as expected I can't endure it! Springtime... gently rolling...
このー！ JK UHK！
Take this! JK UHK!
不安になったんだけど… 大丈夫そう？
I started getting worried... Is she gonna be okay?
あ！ 最後までね！ お、お辞儀！
Ah! Until the end! B-Bow!
最後まで… お、お辞儀！
Until the end... b-bow!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
マジでいろはス ビジネスでよかった〜
Seriously, I'm so glad Iroha-su was just business...
義務、義務。
Duty, duty.
バイバイ。
Bye-bye.
じゃね。帰るね。
See ya. I'm leaving.
プロデューサー: どうしたんですか？
[Producer: What's wrong?]
ねぇねぇ！ プロデューサーの好みってどんな人なん？
Hey, hey! What kind of person is your type, Producer?
プロデューサー: え〜…
[Producer: Uh~...]
ほら、ホロライブっていろんな人いるジャン？
Look, there are so many different people in Hololive, right?
しゅびしゅわ〜。すぅの充電たりてるー？ 水宮すぅだよー！
Shubi-shuwa~! Is Su's charge enough? I'm Mizumiya Su~!
わっしょーい！ ホロライブの清楚担当！ みんなのアイドル〜、夏色〜まつりでーす！
Wasshoi! Hololive's pure idol! Everyone's idol, Natsuiro Matsuri here!
皆さん、待ったかね〜？ ホロライブ6期生 holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します〜！
Everyone, did you wait for me~? Hololive 6th Gen holoX executive, Takane Lui here~!
はーい、みなさま〜、こんらみ〜。 ホロライブ5期生の顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
Hi everyone, kon-Lamy~! Hololive 5th Gen's liver face, Yukihana Lamy here!
Good evening! My Cute students. ちょっこーん！
Good evening! My cute students. Chokkon~!
ホロライブ2期生、悪魔のバーチャル保健医 癒月ちょこでーす！ ちょっこーん！
Hololive 2nd Gen, demon virtual school nurse Yuzuki Choco here! Chokkon~!
Ahoy! ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンでーす！
Ahoy! Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine here~!
プロデューサー: みなさんとっても魅力的ですよ？
[Producer: Everyone is very charming, you know?]
いやいや、そう言うんじゃないでしょ。
No, no, that's not what I mean.
プロデューサー: いやぁ〜仕事ですからね
[Producer: Well, it's work, after all.]
プロデューサー: ホロライブの方で…とかはないですよ
[Producer: I don't have a preference among Hololive members or anything.]
ふーん。
Hmm.
プロデューサー: ただ、最近の趣味といえば…
[Producer: Though, if we're talking about my recent hobby...]
プロデューサー: ＊＊＊＊＊＊
[Producer: * * * * * *]
え…
Huh...
いやぁ…それは…さすがに…すごい趣味してるな…
Well... that's... as expected... quite a heavy hobby...
プロデューサー: この人に言われたくないな…
[Producer: I don't want to hear that from you...]
あ！ こんな時間じゃん！ 吾輩ちょっとこの後用事あるんで…じゃ！
Ah! Look at the time! I have something to do after this... Bye!
初めて呼んじゃったぜ…
I ended up calling for the first time...
やべぇ…
Oh man...
高かった…
It was expensive...
でも 超可愛かったから いっか。
But she was super cute, so it's fine.
ジャケット代とか クリーニング代…
Jacket expenses, cleaning fee...
来ちゃった…
She actually came...
よし！
Alright!
誰ですかー？
Who is it~?
初心者みたいの立ち寄ったんですけど…
She looked like a beginner or something, but...
え？
Eh?
えー！？
Ehh!?
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ ノーサンキュー
Change, change, change, no thank you!
それじゃちょっと息抜きでもしましょうかって感じで
So like, 'Let's take a little break,' I thought,
チラシの番号にTEL
and called the number on the flyer.
たまたまドンピシャで気に入った子がいたんで
There happened to be a girl who was totally my type,
胸の大きい方をチョイス
so I chose the one with big breasts.
髪型ショートで攻めるのが得意な子
A girl with short hair who's good at taking the lead.
『今からそちらへお送りいたします』
'We will send her over to you right now.'
ドアを開けたら別れた彼女
When I opened the door, it was my ex-girlfriend!
おいおいこいつは一体何の冗談だ
Hey, hey, what kind of sick joke is this?!
デリヘル呼んだら君が来た
I ordered a call girl and you showed up!
虚ろな目をして立ってたんだ
Standing there with hollow eyes,
『あなたの好みのタイプになって帰ってきました』って
saying, 'I came back as your exact ideal type.'
ロミジュリばりの悲劇の匂い
Smelling like a tragedy straight out of Romeo and Juliet,
傷つき過ぎたツイストガット
a twisted gut that's been hurt far too much.
街灯を見渡して大声で
Looking around at the streetlights, I shouted:
さあ チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ ノーサンキュー
Now, change, change, change, no thank you!
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ ノーサンキュー
Change, change, change, no thank you!
朝の…
In the morning...
今日はご機嫌 ドレミファソ
Today I'm in a good mood, do-re-mi-fa-so
なかなかの塩梅で
Things are going pretty well
隣の部屋 あえぐのは女子大生
A college girl is moaning in the room next door
ほら今も
Look, even right now
妄想にスレンダーで自傷行為なんだから
Delusory, slender, and self-harming
たまには純情そうな子にしようか
Maybe I'll go with a innocent-looking girl for once
ドアを開けたら 新人の女の子
I opened the door to find a new girl
おいおいどんな魔法を使ったんだよ
Hey, hey, what kind of magic did you use?
ホテヘル行ったら君がいた
I went to a brothel and found you there
うつろな目をして立ってたんだ
Standing there with hollow eyes
「あなたの好みのタイプは全部分かっているのよ」って
"I know all of your favorite types," she said
制服 人妻 ナース OL
School uniform, housewife, nurse, office lady
行く店の品々全部登場
All the choices from the places I go are here
オプションは頼まない
I won't request any options
延長もしない
Nor will I request an extension
行くぞ！
Let's go!
せーの！
Ready, set!
チェンジチェンジチェンジ ノーサンキュー
Change, change, change, no thank you
チェンジチェンジチェンジ ノーサンキュー！
Change, change, change, no thank you!
真夜中起きたら君がいた
When I woke up in the middle of the night, you were there
うつろな目をして立ってたんだ
Standing there with hollow eyes
「あなたの好みのタイプになって帰ってきました」って
"I've returned after becoming your favorite type," she said
思い出したくもない笑顔が
A smile I don't even want to remember
トラウマとなって住みついた
Settled in as a trauma
愛執を見出して
Finding attachment
清算を募集中
Looking for closure
せーの！
Ready, set!
チェンジチェンジチェンジ ノーサンキュー
Change, change, change, no thank you
チェンジチェンジチェンジ ノーサンキュー！
Change, change, change, no thank you!
マジか...
Seriously...?
マジだな...
It really is...
いや、いいんだよ、プロデューサーの好みとか！
No, it's fine, if that's the producer's preference or whatever!
聞いたのは、そっちです
You were the one who asked.
ちょっとちょっと、ケンカしてどうしたの！
Hey, hey! What are you two fighting about?
あっ、こよちゃんー！！！聞いてよー、プロデューサーのやつがー！！！
Ah, Koyo-chan! Listen to this! That producer guy...!
うんうん
Mm-hmm.
それで、あいつがさ〜！
And then, that guy was like...!
そうだね〜、ラブちゃん辛かったね〜
I see~ That must've been tough, Lap-chan~
はぁ、ここまでいろんなホロメンと絡んできたけど
*Sigh*, I've hung out with so many Holo-members up until now...
やっぱりこよちゃんが一番だよ！！
But Koyo-chan really is the best!!
そうだ！今度の吾輩の生誕ライブ一緒に出ようよ！こよちゃんと吾輩にぴったりな曲があるんだ！
I know! Come perform in my upcoming Birthday Live with me! I have the perfect song for us!
ライブの出演ね！スケジュール･･･確認しておくね～！
Appearing in your Live? I'll... check my schedule~!
ありがとー！じゃあまたステージで！！
Thank you! See you on stage then!!
（俺、このライブが終わったら･･･君と･･･）
(Once this Live is over... with you...)
時計の針が
The hands of the clock
12から12に回るまで
Turn from 12 to 12
頭の中が
Inside my head
染められていく ぴんこすてぃっくLuv
Is getting dyed, Pinko Stick Luv
すれ違ったり
Passing each other by
ふと目と目が交わるだけで
Or just our eyes accidentally meeting
宙に浮いてる気分になる
Makes me feel like I'm floating in mid-air
でもそんなこと君は知らないし
But you don't even know that
Say yeah!
手を繋ぎたい
I want to hold hands
キスをしたい
I want to kiss
君と半径10メートル以内
Within a 10-meter radius of you
でも叶わない だから妄想で
But it won't come true, so in my delusions
今日も蛇口とキスの練習day
Today is another day of practicing kissing with the faucet
君のことに一喜一憂
Swooning and worrying over everything about you
だって好きだから！
Because I like you!
こっち向いて
Look this way
まってまって
Wait, wait
やっぱ向いて！
Still, look this way!
独り占めしたいの
I want to have you all to myself
こっち向いて
Look this way
わがままだって
Even if I'm being selfish
分かってるけど
I know it, but...
だってだってだってだって！
'Cause, 'cause, 'cause, 'cause!
目が合って
Our eyes meet
高鳴って
My heart throbs
赤くなって
I blush red
百面相してるの
Making all sorts of faces
今日だって
Today as well
君のせいで
It's all your fault
ドキドキ忙しい どうしてくれるの
My heart's fluttering so frantically, what are you gonna do about it?
サンデー マンデー チュースデイ ウェンズデイ 毎日クリンチ ギュッとして
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, clinching every day, hold me tight
ぬいてけ9時 けにけさキューティ 12にぼっち あっちいっそっち こっち向いてどっち？
Let's go, 9 o'clock, cute and sweet, alone at 12, over there, look over here, which way?
BPM 日に日に好きになるS.N.S
BPM, day by day I like you more on social media
分かったよなんて自分勝手 やっぱりきっぱりピンクにしよっ！
"I get it" is so selfish, let's definitely make it pink!
ピンクを君に伝えたい
I want to convey pink to you
ピンク脳内戦境 レベルは最強 テストが勉強 許してよ愛嬌
Pink brain battle, level is max, testing my studying, forgive my charm
待ちに待った今日 君とランデブー ご一緒なんて妄想です 枕元のショー！
The long-awaited today, a rendezvous with you, dreaming of being together, a bedside show!
こっち向いて 待って待って
Look this way, wait, wait
やっぱ向いて 恥ずかしいけど
Turn around after all, though I'm embarrassed
どっち向いて 君の目に映った
Which way are you facing? Reflected in your eyes...
自分の顔が赤い気がして
...I feel like my own face is turning red
目が合った 照れ隠した 照れた分だけ
Our eyes met, hid my shyness, as much as I blushed...
1対1のロンリーナイト
...a one-on-one lonely night
だって 君のことが この先ずっと好きだなんて言えないの！
Because I can't bring myself to say I'll love you forever!
枕の裏 思い浮かべて 好きだよ 好きなのね
Picture it under the pillow, I love you, I really do
想うだけで幸せなの ほんと ちょっと切ない
Just thinking of it makes me happy, but honestly a bit bittersweet
口強がる強がりにぬいて 寂しがり実はもう限界
Acting tough on the outside, but I'm lonely and at my limit
超えてるんだけど
...though I've already crossed it
言えるはずない 言えるわけない
There's no way I can say it, I could never say it
臆病なハートに後押ししてよ罪
Give my timid heart a push, it's a sin
こっち向いて 待って待って
Look this way, wait, wait
やっぱ向いて 独り占めしたいの
Turn around after all, I want you all to myself
こっち向いて ワガママだって
Look this way, even if it's selfish
分かってるけど だってだってだってだって
I know it is, but still, still, still!
目が合った 照れ隠して 赤くなって
Our eyes met, hiding my blush, turning red
夢と知ってるの 今日もだって
I know it's a dream, even today
君のせいで 時々騒がしい
Because of you, it gets noisy at times
神様お願い ちょっとでいいから 勇気をください
God, please, just a little bit, give me courage
ガチ気まぐれ
Totally whimsical!
プロデューサー あぁぁ！！！
Producer, aaah!
プロデューサー: どうしたんですか？
[Producer: What happened?]
こよちゃんにフラれたぁ〜
Koyo-chan rejected me~!
プロデューサー: フラれるとかあるんですね？
[Producer: You actually got rejected?]
ちくしょう！！！こうなったら！！！
Damn it!!! If it's come to this...!!!
プロデューサー: 嫌な予感がする
[Producer: I have a bad feeling about this...]
誰でもいいから付き合いたい〜！！
I'll date anyone! Just go out with me~!
プロデューサー: そうなったらもう終わりですよ
[Producer: If you do that, it's over.]
うるさい！吾輩は･･･彼女作って幸せになるんだー！！！！！
Shut up! I'm going to get a girlfriend and be happy!!!!!
やるぞ･･･ 緊張する･･･ やってやる！
Let's do this... I'm nervous... I'm gonna do it!
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I don't care who, someone go out with me!
もう誰でもいいから
Somebody, anybody!
男の前では喋れても 女の前では喋れない
I can talk in front of guys, but not girls.
トラウマだらけの僕の過去 涙なしでは語れない
My traumatized past can't be told without tears.
「どうして彼女ができないの？」 僕は素敵だと君は言う
"Why can't you get a girlfriend? You're great," you say.
「それなら僕と付き合ってよ」 その苦笑の意味はなに
"Then why not date me?" What's that awkward smile for?
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I don't care who, someone go out with me!
もう誰でもいいから
Somebody, anybody!
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I don't care who, someone go out with me!
誰でもいいから
Somebody, anybody!
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I don't care who, someone go out with me!
もう誰でもいいから
Somebody, anybody!
もう誰でもいいから！！
Somebody, anybody!!
なんで･･･ なんでだよあぁぁ！！
Why... Why, aaah!!
全員からフラれたぁぁぁ〜〜〜！！！
Everyone rejected me~~~!!!
プロデューサー: うーん、このライブ、大丈夫かな
[Producer: Hmm, is this live concert going to be okay...]
くそ、もうこうなったら！
Damn it, if it's come to this!
プロデューサー: えぇ！？なんですかそれ！
[Producer: EH?! What is that?!]
この封印を･･･解放してやるぅ！！！
I'm going to... unseal this power!!!
俺の聖槌を･･･爆裂させてやるぅ！！！ ウォーーーー！！！
I'll make my holy hammer explode! Raaaaaaagh!!!
プロデューサー: お、おしまいだこのライブは･･･ もはやライブなのかも怪しい所･･･
[Producer: Th-This concert is finished... I'm not even sure if this can be called a concert anymore...]
聖槍爆裂ボーイ
[Sacred Spear Explosion Boy]
なんていうか大きな声で言うことではないかもしれませんが
I might not be something to say out loud, but...
男女に備わったあれとそれ
That and this equipped to men and women,
正と乱のいわばあれとそれ
so to speak, that and this of order and chaos.
そんなこんなで起こるハプニング
Such happenings that occur through this and that,
あっという間に僕のエンディング
and in the blink of an eye, my ending.
謝って 悩んで 困ってしまって どうしようって何もできない無情
Apologizing, worrying, getting troubled, and helpless to do anything...
0.02mmの壁がすげーもどかしくなって
The 0.02mm wall gets super frustrating,
真っ赤なMy sunshine すぐに入れたくなるのは君のせい
my bright red My Sunshine—wanting to put it in right away is your fault.
いいじゃーんとかそんな気分で迎えた君と僕 そんなヘブンで
Welcoming with a "Why not?" mood, you and me in such a heaven,
あ、しまっ破って思ってももう遅い
Ah, thinking "Oh crap!" is already too late.
Upside inside out. I defend you.
甘噛みyouの髪 一切合切は愛で返事
Gently biting your hair, replying to everything with love,
I'm coming. You're coming.
待ってこれって僕のせい？
Wait, is this my fault?
生でいいよって言った君のせい？
Or your fault for saying "unprotected is fine"?
そして5分で終わるテストって 信憑性欠けるもんだって
And a 5-minute test lacks credibility, they say.
しっかり刻まれた十字架に 貼り付けられた僕は切り捨てに
Nailed to a deeply carved cross, I'm cast aside,
なったって無理ってわかっているって どうしようって何もできない
knowing it's impossible, helpless to do anything.
0.02mmの壁がすげー悩ましくなって
The 0.02mm wall gets super agonizing,
真っ青なMy sunshine すぐに入れたくなるのは僕の性
my deep blue My Sunshine—wanting to put it in right away is my nature.
大丈夫とかそんな気分で 甲斐性もないこんな身分で
Feeling like "It'll be fine", with no capability in this position,
泣いたって怒ったって後の祭り
crying or getting mad won't change anything now.
Maximum insert なう。
Maximum insert now.
Are you ready? 愛撫ハニー 指噛み
Are you ready? Caressing honey, biting fingers,
聖槍爆裂ボーイ
Sacred Spear Explosion Boy.
愛がfeeling. I've honey. You be coming.
Love feeling. I've honey. You be coming.
遠い夏の思い出
Memories of a distant summer,
君の長い髪が揺れる
your long hair sways.
待ってこれって僕のせい？
Wait, is this my fault?
中に出してって言った君のせい？
Or your fault for saying "cum inside"?
そして5分で終わるテストって
And a 5-minute test,
絶対的二元論だって
they say it's an absolute dualism.
十月十日ばかりの運命を 支配している僕は神様に
Controlling a destiny of ten months and ten days,
なれないって無理ってわかっていて 結局何も解決してない
I can't become God, knowing it's impossible, resolving nothing in the end.
0.02mmの壁がすげーもどかしくなって
The 0.02mm wall gets super frustrating,
真っ白なMy sunshine すぐに入れたくなるのは君のせい
my pure white My Sunshine—wanting to put it in right away is your fault.
いいじゃーんとかそんな気分で 迎えた君と僕 そんなヘブンで
Welcoming with a "Why not?" mood, you and me in such a heaven,
あ、しまっ破って思ってももう遅い
Ah, thinking "Oh crap!" is already too late.
Upside inside out. I defend you.
甘噛みyouの髪 一切合切は愛で返事
Gently biting your hair, replying to everything with love,
I'm coming. You're coming.
Maximum insert なう。
Maximum insert now.
Are you ready? 愛撫ハニー 指噛み
Are you ready? Caressing honey, biting fingers,
聖槍爆裂ボーイ
Sacred Spear Explosion Boy.
愛がfeeling. I've honey. You be coming.
Love feeling. I've honey. You be coming.
いやあ、まさか、聖槍でライブ会場壊しちゃうなんて
Man, I can't believe you destroyed the live venue with Seisou...
つい…力を解放してしまった…
I accidentally... unleashed my power...
それにしても、みんなひどくない？吾輩を振るなんて…もうやってらんないよ～
Even so, isn't everyone so cruel? Ditching me like that... I can't take this anymore~
(ここはあの手を使うしかない)
(I guess I have no choice but to use that trick...)
ラプラスさん、実は、あの方に来ていただいてます！
La+-san, to tell you the truth, we have that person here today!
あの方？
That person?
ラブくん？どうしたのー？
Lab-kun? What's wrong?
うわっ！？あ、あ、あじゅ姉！？まさか、吾輩のために来てくれたの？？？？
Whoa!? A-A-Aju-nee!? Don't tell me you came here just for my sake????
当然だよー！だって今日は、ラブくんの誕生日でしょー？
Of course! I mean, today is Lab-kun's birthday, right?
あ、やばい、吾輩今日が命日かもしれん・・・・
Ah, crap... today might be the day I die of bliss...
お誕生日おめでとう！プレゼントは何がいいのかな～？
Happy birthday! What would you like as a present?
え！プレゼントってなんでももらえるの？！
What! I can get anything as a present?!
あじゅがあげられるものなら何でも大丈夫だぞ☆
Anything Aju can give you is fine! ☆
えー！！えええ！じゃあ
Woah!! Eeee! Then...
え？今なんて言ったの？変な音で聞こえなかった！
Huh? What did you just say? I couldn't hear over that weird sound!
あれ？
Huh?
なんだこれー！届かないぞ吾輩の願いが！
What is this?! My wish isn't getting through!
あぶない…危なく配信できないところだった…
That was close... We almost couldn't air the stream...
邪魔をするなプロデューサーーー！！！！！
Get out of the way, Producer!!!!!
なんか色々大変そうだから…今日はこの辺で帰るね！今日は本当におめでと～！ラブくん、また遊ぼうね～
It seems like things are crazy here... so I'll head home for today! Happy birthday once again! Lab-kun, let's hang out again~
帰るね。
I'm going home now.
今日は本当におめでとう。
Congratulations on today, truly.
ラプくん、また遊ぼうね～
Lap-kun, let's play again~
あ、あじゅねぇ！あじゅねぇぇぇぇぇ！！！！
Ah, Aju-nee! Aju-neeeee!!
え、はい、はい、分からました！
Eh, yes, yes, I understand!
ラプラスさん！新曲オーディションですって！
Laplus-san! They said there's a new song audition!
どゆこと！？
What do you mean!?
新曲だけのオーディション大会があって、そこで優勝したら、大型コラボですって！
There's an audition contest with new songs, and if you win, it's a major collab!
今すぐ曲準備します！
I'll prepare a song right away!
ダンスレッスンいれますね！
I'll schedule dance lessons too!
今から新曲？ダンスレッスン？
A new song now? Dance lessons?
ま、間に合うのそれ？
W-Will we make it in time?
もうライブまでちょっとしかないよ？
There's barely any time left before the live show!
間に合わせてください！もしオーディションに合格したら大型コラボなんですよ！！
Please make it in time! If you pass the audition, it's a huge collaboration!!
えー！！吾輩もう疲れたんですけど！！
What!! I'm already tired though!!
大型コラボってなんなの！！
What is this major collab anyway?!
それはまだ、秘密です。
That's still a secret.
なんでだよおおお！！！！
Whyyyyy?!
…はぁ、、はぁ、、体力ないって言ってるのに、、走り込み…？
...*Puff*, *pant*... I said I have no stamina, so why running...?
だからこその走り込みです！
That's precisely why you're running!
…はぁ、この筋トレ、、本当に意味あるの？
...*Sigh*, does this weight training really have any point?
…だっ、、はぁ、、あああ、、
...Gah, *pant*, ahhh...
よし！良い感じだ！
Alright! Looking good!
ラプラスさん！本番前に行きましょう！あの方の元へ！
Laplus-san! Let me take you to that person before the main show!
あ、あの方！？
Ah, that person!?
あ～よし！行こう！！
Ah~ alright! Let me go!!
ちょこ先生ー！
Choco-sensei~!
あら、いらっしゃい、ラッちゃん。
My, welcome, Lap-chan.
どれにするの？
Which one will you pick?
悩むわよね～
It's hard to decide, isn't it~
分かる、分かる～
I know, I know~
答えは一つじゃないからね～
Because there isn't just one answer~
ラッちゃん、真剣に考えたのね～
Lap-chan, you really thought about it seriously, didn't you~
え？全部ちゃんと見たいの？
Eh? You want to see all of them properly?
じゃあ、皆さんお待ちかねのグッズ情報よ～
Then, here is the merch info everyone's been waiting for~
ラッちゃんー！
Lap-chan~!
はーい！はいはいはい！
Yesss! Yes yes yes!
ラプラス・ダークネス 誕生日記念2026グッズ！
Laplus Darkness Birthday Celebration 2026 Goods!
順番に紹介していきます！
We'll introduce them one by one!
じゃん！まずはこちら、カードアルバムー！
Ta-da! First, this one: Card Album~!
特典のあのチェキ風ブロマイドカードとか、ホロカとかを収納できるアルバムです！
It's an album where you can store bonus polaroid-style bromide cards, HoloCards, and such!
えっと、めっちゃ久しぶりに黒星先生が、えっと吾輩のママね！黒星ママが、描き下ろしてくださいましたイラスト！
Um, after a super long time, Kuroboshi-sensei—my mama, you know! Kuroboshi-mama drew a new illustration for this!
イェーイ！めっちゃかわいい！
Yay! So cute!
かわいいでしょ～
Isn't it cute~?
や、このアルバムぎゅっと生活してるのがまたいいで。
Yeah, hugging this album like that is so nice.
そうでしょ！これもちゃんと、あのアルバムをぎゅっと心でしてるんですよ。
Right! She's tightly hugging that album in this illustration too.
じゃあ、これ買ったらラッちゃんがぎゅっとしたアルバムが手に入っるってこと？
So if I buy this, I get the album that Lap-chan is hugging?
え？
Eh?
それはあの、商品情報…
That's, um, product info...
2つ目はこちら！
Second item is this!
興奮ボイスキーホルダー！えー、毎回おなじみの撮り下ろしボイスが6種類入ったキーホルダーです！
Excitement Voice Keychain! Um, it's the familiar keychain with 6 newly recorded voices!
え、押すと声が出ます。いつも通り。今回もしろこ先生の描き下ろしです！
Um, press it and a voice plays. As usual. Drawn by Shiroko-sensei again!
メロメロな表情をしたオリジナルのぬまっち姿です！
It's an original numatch figure with a smitten expression!
押すと声が出る。
Pressing it makes a sound.
はい。
Yes.
へぇ～！どこを押したらいいのかな～？
Heeh~! Where should I press, I wonder~?
え！？
Eh!?
どこ…っ！みっつめは！みっつめはこちら！
Where...! The third one! The third one is this!
え、ばぶラプラスぬいぐるみです！えっと、おしゃぶりを加えて、ベビーウェアを着て寝ている吾輩のぬいぐるみでございます！
Um, it's the Baby Laplus Plushie! Um, it's a plushie of me wearing baby clothes with a pacifier and sleeping!
え、めっちゃかわいいー！チョコもぎゅーってしたい！
Eh, so cute~! Choco wants to hug it tightly too!
ちょ、ちょ、先生、そんな…いつでも…いつでも…
Wait, Sensei, not like that... anytime... anytime...
あぁ～！あぁ、いい匂いするぅ…
Ahhh~! Ah, it smells so good...
やめてください！
Please stop!
本当に…っ、もう、まずい、まずい。
Really... geez, bad, bad.
よっつめはこちら！
Fourth item is this!
えー、ばぶラプラスぬいぐるみを包めるハンカチです！
Um, it's a handkerchief that can wrap up the Baby Laplus Plushie!
さっきのぬいぐるみをね、包めて、あとは普通にハンカチとしても使えます。
You can wrap the plushie from earlier, and you can also use it normally as a handkerchief.
あ、じゃあ、おくるみとして使えるってことね？
Ah, so it can be used as a swaddling blanket?
そうです。
That's right.
かわいいー！
Cute~!
でか、でかいっす。たぶんこんなしかないっす。
It's big. It's probably about this big.
そして最後に、フルセット購入特典として、えー、黒星紅白ママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきまーす！
And lastly, as a full set purchase bonus, a polaroid-style bromide card drawn by Kuroboshi Kouhaku-mama is included~!
はい、そして数量限定版は、はい、書きます！サインを！直筆サインと複写メッセージが入ってまーす！
Yes, and for the limited quantity version, yes, I'll write on them! A handwritten signature and a printed message will be included!
通常バージョンは
The regular version
箔押しの複製サインとメッセージが入ってるよ
comes with a foil-stamped duplicated signature and message!
この配信の後に販売開始だから
Sales will begin right after this stream,
みんな、よろしくねー！
so everyone, please check it out!
お願いします
Please do!
はい、以上グッズ紹介なんですけど
Alright, that's it for the merch introduction,
チョコ先生、ありがとうございます
Choco-sensei, thank you very much!
ええ、こちらこそ！
No, thank you!
ありがとうございます。これからちょっとオーディションなんで、新曲の
Thank you! I have an audition for my new song next...
お！頑張って！
Ooh! Good luck!
応援してるね、ラプちゃん！頑張って！
I'm cheering for you, Lap-chan! Good luck!
頑張ります！ありがとう！
I'll do my best! Thank you!
頑張れー！
Good luck!
お姉さま♡ラヴコール
Big Sister ♡ Love Call
あ、お姉さま！
Ah, Big Sister!
あの、今日ライブなのに我が輩お風呂入ってないんですけど
Um, even though it's a concert today, I haven't taken a bath...
お願いがあって、はぁてへへ...
and I have a request, teehee...
あの、耳舐めてほしいです！
Um, I want you to lick my ears!
お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
すーはー すーはー
*sniff sniff, inhale exhale*
お姉さま♡ お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
お・ね・え・さ・ま~~~~!
B-i-g S-i-s-t-e-r~~~~!
世の中のお姉さまに捧ぐ
Dedicated to all the big sisters in the world!
あ、お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Ah, Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
起きたら耳元でささやいて
When I wake up, whisper in my ear.
あ、お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Ah, Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
うなじに滴るその汗を
That sweat dripping down the nape of your neck,
我が輩のお紅茶に入れてゴックンゴックンしたい！
I want to drop it into my tea and gulp it down!
ツノ ツノ ツノ 掴んでちょうだい
Grab my horns, grab them, grab them please!
ハンドル代わりに
Use them as handlebars,
お！お！お！
Oh! Oh! Oh!
あ、あ、お姉様と視聴者の皆さま...
Ah, Big Sister and all the viewers...
こんな歌ライブで歌ってごめんなさい！
I'm so sorry for singing a song like this live!
あ、お仕置き！お仕置きください！
Ah, punishment! Please punish me!
尻尾からてっぺんまでガタガタ揺さぶってください ツノを！
Shake my horns violently from my tail to the tip!
あ、お姉様今日ニーハイですか！
Ah, Big Sister, are you wearing thigh-highs today?!
盛り上がってきましたね！
It's getting exciting!
え！お姉様！お姉様方！あ、お世話になっております！
Eh! Big Sister! Big Sisters! Ah, thank you for your support!
ありがたや さぁさぁ ありがたや
How thankful, come on, how thankful!
おいでなすってお姉さま
Welcome, Big Sister!
雑魚雑魚言ってください
Please call me weakling, weakling!
残さず飲み込むゾ 愛のムチ
I'll swallow every bit of your whip of love!
ムチムチ 愛のムチ
Sensual, whip of love!
お願いなぶってお姉さま
Please tease me, Big Sister!
キモくてごめんなさい
I'm sorry for being gross!
ありのままで キャストオフ！
Just as I am, cast off!
お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
すーはー すーはー
*sniff sniff, inhale exhale*
お姉さま♡ お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
お・ね・え・さ・ま~~~~!
B-i-g S-i-s-t-e-r~~~~!
注目せよ！
Pay attention!
YMDはもう古い！
YMD is already old news!
時代はYSOだ！
The era of YSO is here!
YSOとは何か？
What is YSO?
そう！やたらセクシーなお姉さま！
That's right! Extremely Sexy Big Sister!
YSO! YSO! YSO!
YY YY YY YSO
お姉さま お姉さま やたらセクシーなお姉さま！
Big Sister! Big Sister! Extremely sexy Big Sister!
ほんわか ドジっ子 姉御肌
Warm-hearted, clumsy, big-sisterly type,
クーデレ ツンデレ 小悪魔系
Cool-headed, tsundere, impish type...
いろんなお姉がいるけれど
There are all kinds of big sisters, but...
あらあら ウフフが 優勝ですw
"Ara ara, ufufu" takes the crown! lol
もち肌！ ぽにぽに
Soft skin! Squishy-squishy
太もも？ スリスリ
Thighs? Rub-rub
ギューして！ むにむに
Hug me! Squeeze-squeeze
居なきゃリャ？ 無理無理イイイ
Without them? Impossible, impossible, nooo!
ああん、お姉さまがいない世界なんて 耐えられないでちゅううう！！！
Ahn, I can't stand a world without Big Sister!!!
そうして、我が輩は、赤ちゃんになった。
And so, I became a baby.
なぜなら、よしよしされる幸せな世界。
Because it's a happy world where I get cuddled and praised.
今日もまた、お姉さまの太ももに顔をうずめ、
Today as well, burying my face in Big Sister's thighs,
よだれをたらす。これが、人生なのだ。
I drool. This is what life is all about.
キモく たしかに 美しく
Grossly, surely, beautifully,
おいでって言って お姉さま
say "come here", Big Sister!
抱っこ抱っこしてください
Hold me, hug me, please!
本能が剥き出しゾ
My instincts are laid bare!
脚のムチムチ 胸のムチ
Sensual thighs, sensual chest!
失礼しまッス お姉さま
Pardon me, Big Sister!
全裸でごめんなさい
I'm sorry for being completely naked!
ありのままで キャストオフ！
Just as I am, cast off!
愛してます お姉さま♡
I love you, Big Sister ♡
お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
すーはー すーはー
*sniff sniff, inhale exhale*
お姉さま♡ お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
やたらセクシーなお姉さま♡
Extremely sexy Big Sister ♡
お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
すーはー すーはー
*sniff sniff, inhale exhale*
お姉さま♡ お姉さま♡ あぁ お姉さま♡
Big Sister ♡ Big Sister ♡ Ah, Big Sister ♡
お・ね・え・さ・ま~~~~!
B-i-g S-i-s-t-e-r~~~~!
ばぶー
Babu...
と言うことで 新曲を披露させていただきました
So with that, I've just performed my new song!
タイトルは「お姉様♡ラブコード」です！
The title is "Onee-sama ♡ Love Code"!
ちゃんと「お姉様」の後にハートが付くやつです
It's the one with a heart right after "Onee-sama".
P丸様。さんと まのさんに作ってもらいました
It was made for me by P-Maru-sama and Mano!
依頼した時は「最近のラプラスさんを見てたら 楽しく作れました」みたいに言ってくれました
When I requested it, they told me, "Watching you lately made it really fun to write!"
とんでもない曲になっちゃったぜ！
It turned into an incredible song!
収録の時も… あ これまあ後でリリースされるんですけど 収録する時もね
Even during recording... Ah, well, it'll be released later, but even during recording...
「もっとキモく！もっと内なるお姉様への思いを込めながら歌ってください」とか言われて
I was told, "Make it creepier! Sing with more of your inner feelings for your Onee-sama!"
あんなディレクションは初めてでした
I've never received direction like that before!
そんな曲がこの後 MVが私のチャンネルでプレミア公開されますよ！
That song's MV will premiere on my channel right after this!
そして 今日25日なんですけれど 明日26日に日付が変わった瞬間に この楽曲がリリースされてしまいます！
And today is the 25th, but as soon as the date changes to tomorrow, the 26th, this song will be released!
更に！なんと！まあサムネにもね ちょっと釣りみたいな感じで重重大告知みたいに書いたんですけど
Furthermore! Believe it or not! I wrote a clickbaity "Major Announcement" on the thumbnail...
なんと！ついに！私 ラプラス・ダークネス 1人で初めてのアルバムが発売されるぜ！イエーイ！
Believe it or not! Finally! I, La+ Darknesss, will be releasing my very first solo album! Yay!
1年に1曲しかオリ曲出さなかったのに 去年狂ったようにオリ曲出して 今年も出して アルバムが出せるようになるなんて 感慨深いでございます
I used to release only one original song a year, but after releasing them like crazy last year and continuing this year, being able to release an album is deeply moving!
そして なんと今回は2種類出るんだけど
And believe it or not, this time it comes in two versions!
1つ目がね ラプラス・ダークネス 1st Album『ラブ様 アーティスト化計画』高いやつ！
The first one is La+ Darknesss 1st Album "Love-sama Artistification Project" - The Expensive One!
ということで 高いやつです
So yeah, that's the expensive version.
で もう1つが『ラブ様 アーティスト化計画』安いやつ！
And the other one is "Love-sama Artistification Project" - The Cheap One!
ということで まぁちょっとお金を… 持っている大きいお友達用のアルバムと
So, um, well... a version for "big friends" who have extra money...
まぁお金 ちょっとママにお願いしようかなー「ママ買ってー」みたいな感じでお願いできそうな値段の
...and a version priced so you can ask your mom, "Mom, please buy this for me!"
ホロライブで出てるアルバムだと一番安いんじゃない？っていうぐらい安いやつ！の2種類があるよ！
It's so cheap it might be the cheapest album ever released in Hololive! There are these two versions!
この配信のあとからホロライブ公式ショップで予約開始だから みんな予約してねー！
Pre-orders start on the Hololive official shop right after this stream, so everyone please pre-order!
詳しくはホームページをチェック！
Check the official website for details!
さっき披露した新曲も もちろんアルバムに入るぜ！
The new song I performed earlier will also be included in the album!
さ 新曲オーディションは終わったしな
Well, the new song audition is over.
あとは結果待つだけなんで じゃね バイバイ！
Now I just have to wait for the results. See ya, bye-bye!
お疲れ！なんか優勝したらね ご褒美って言ってたんだあ きっと 何だろうなー
Good job! They said there'd be a reward if I won. I wonder what it'll be.
やりましね！優勝ですよ！
[Producer] You did it! You won!
流石にレッスンとか急ぎすぎたって～… もうへとへと…
The lessons and schedule were way too rushed... I'm totally exhausted...
…はい、分かりました！ ラプラスさん…
[Producer] ...Yes, I understand! La+-san...
ん？
Hm?
今すぐいきますよ！！大型コラボの現場へ！！！
[Producer] We're heading out right now!! To the big collaboration venue!!!
え？ なに？ え、なになに？ どこ行くのー？？？
Huh? What? Uh, what what? Where are we going???
みんなー、こんばんはー！
Hello, everyone! Good evening!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming!
短い時間だけど、一緒に楽しもうね！
It's a short time, but let's have fun together!
今日は特別なゲストが来てくれています！
Tonight, we have a very special guest!
ホロライブのラプラス・ダークネスさんです！
From Hololive, it's La+ Darknesss-san!
り、りなみさん？
R-Rinami-san?
あ、本当に...本物のりなみさんですか？
Ah, really... Are you the real Rinami-san?
はい！初めまして！
Yes! Nice to meet you!
あ、初めまして...
Ah, nice to meet you...
今日はご一緒できて光栄です！
It's an honor to perform with you today!
なんて呼んだらいいですか？
What should I call you?
あ、敬語はやめてください。吾輩のことはラプ君って呼んでください。
Ah, please drop the formal speech. Please call me Lap-kun.
吾輩も、りなみお姉さんって呼んでもいいですか？
Can I call you Rinami Onee-san too?
もちろん！りなみお姉さんって呼んでくれると嬉しいな！ラプ君！
Of course! I'd love it if you called me Rinami Onee-san! Lap-kun!
りなみお姉さん...はい...
Rinami Onee-san... yes...
ラプ君！
Lap-kun!
今日は私の曲を披露させてもらうんだけど、ラプ君も会場を盛り上げるために、ちょっとだけ一緒に参加してくれるんだよね？
Today I'll be performing my song, but Lap-kun, you'll join in a bit to help hype up the crowd, right?
はい！恐縮です！本当はこんな近くで見れるだけでも嬉しいんですけど...
Yes! I'm honored! Honestly, I'm happy just watching from this close, but...
微力ながら参加させていただきます！
I'll do my best to participate!
うん！一緒に共演できて嬉しいよ！
Yay! I'm so glad we can perform together!
素敵なライブになるといいね！
I hope it turns out to be a wonderful show!
はい！
Yes!
それじゃあ、早速1曲披露させてもらおうかな！
Well then, shall I perform the first song right away?
ラプ君、準備はいい？
Lap-kun, are you ready?
はい、もちろんです！行きます！準備します！
Yes, of course! Here I go! I'll get ready!
みんなも一緒に楽しもうね！
Everyone, let's have fun together!
それでは1曲目...聴いてください！
Now then, for the first song... Please listen!
I know 愛のボーダー
I know love's border
今日は少しだけ飛び越えてみちゃおうっか
Today, shall we try jumping over it just a little?
全然ハジマンナイ物語を見ているような気分
It feels like I'm watching a story that hasn't even begun
鈍感な君にお知らせします
Here's a notice for dense little you
このままいけばエンドロールで YOU=エキストラ A
If things go on like this, in the end credits YOU = Extra A
すぐ逸らすその目も
That gaze of yours that quickly turns away
待てど出ないロマンスの芽も
And the sprout of romance that never appears no matter how long I wait
「ねぇねぇ、ちょっとおでこ貸して♪」でラブもデコっちゃう？
"Hey, hey, lend me your forehead for a bit♪" Should we decorate our love too?
急な「ぎゅっ」でキュンも cute 私の cue 受け取ってよ
A sudden "squeeze" makes it cute, take my cue!
予感に身を委ねてみたいの
I want to surrender myself to this premonition
私からモーションじゃ王道すぎるでしょ？
If I make the move, it's too classic, right?
36℃ ウブな君に caution!
36℃ Caution to innocent you!
もうちょい私にお熱をあげて欲しいのです
I want you to get a little more passionate about me
君にとって私一体何なの？
What on earth am I to you?
はい、ど〜ぞここからは君の番
Yes, go ahead, from here it's your turn
上手く言おうなんてしないで
Don't try to say it perfectly
ちょっと不自然くらいじゃなきゃ
If it's not a little bit awkward
恋なんてそう始まりようがないもの
Love couldn't possibly start like that
出来不出来は横に置いて 耽溺を希望
Leaving skill aside, I hope for total obsession
ちょっと high な熱い love にうなされてみない？
Won't you try being feverish with a slightly high, burning love?
キホンのキホン 恋の三大 chachacha
The absolute basics, love's three big cha-cha-chas
chance・chase・challenge
Chance, chase, challenge
用のないメッセージ さりげないタッチ
Meaningless messages, casual touches
翻訳すればすべてが つまりラビュー
If you translate it, everything means "Love You"
頭で考えずに脊髄反射で応えて
Don't think with your head, respond with a reflex
no, no だけじゃ能がないよ
Saying "no, no" all the time is useless
そうよあとちょっと もう一歩
That's it, just a little more, one step closer
3・2・1で
At 3, 2, 1!
cha cha cha cha cha
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha
やればできる子素直でよろしい
You can do it if you try, good job being honest
36℃ ニブい君に caution!
36℃ Caution to dense you!
「どうせ・だって・でもでも」なんて 3D を抜け出して
Break free from the 3D excuses like "Anyway, because, but but"
異次元的ステキをいっぱい感じて
Feel lots of otherworldly wonder
はい、ど〜ぞここからは君の番
Yes, go ahead, from here it's your turn
「違うかも…」なんて構えないで
Don't overthink with "Maybe I'm wrong..."
ちょっとくらいの勘違いがなきゃ
Without a little bit of misunderstanding
恋なんてそう始まりようがないもの
Love couldn't possibly start like that
ラプ君、お誕生日おめでとう！
Lap-kun, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
一緒にクラップ！
Clap along together!
「ねぇねぇ、ちょっとおでこ貸して♪」でラブもデコっちゃう？
"Hey, hey, lend me your forehead for a bit♪" Should we decorate our love too?
「ぎゅっ」でキュンも cute 私の cue 受け取ってよ
A sudden "squeeze" makes it cute, take my cue!
予感に身を委ねてみたいの
I want to surrender myself to this premonition
私からモーションじゃ王道すぎるでしょ？
If I make the move, it's too classic, right?
36℃ウブな君に caution!
Caution to you, so naive at 36℃!
もうちょい私にお熱を上げて欲しいのです
I want you to fall a little crazier for me.
余裕に見えて
Even if I seem composed,
私もいっぱいいっぱいで
I'm actually completely overwhelmed.
はい少々 本音を打ち明けちゃう
Alright, I'll reveal a bit of my true feelings.
完璧なお姉さんだって
Even a perfect older sister...
ちょっとくらいの隙がなくっちゃ
needs to have a few flaws,
好きになんてなれるはずがないものでしょ？
otherwise how could anyone fall for her, right?
だから君を
So I'm waiting for you,
“スキ”だらけで待っています いつだって
completely full of openings for love, anytime.
ちょっとhighな熱いloveにうなされてみたい
I want to be swept away by a slightly high, burning love.
36℃ U・B・Uでした〜！
That was "36℃ U・B・U"!
どうだったかな〜？
How was it~?
最高でしたー！
It was the best!
ラプくん、ありがとう！
Rapu-kun, thank you!
一緒にパフォーマンスしてくれて嬉しいよ！
I'm so glad you performed with me!
はっ、あの！黒子で楽しかったです！
Ah, um! Being a stagehand was so much fun!
あの、間近で李波さんのパフォーマンス見れて、もう、光栄でした！
Um, seeing Ribo-san's performance up close was such an honor!
ふふっ、ありがとう！
Hehe, thank you!
えっと、今日は次の曲が最後になるんだけど...
Um, today's next song will be the last one...
えー！
What?!
早すぎます！まだ見たいです！
That's too fast! I want to see more!
ん〜、名残惜しいけど...
Mmm, I hate to say goodbye, but...
次の曲は、みんなにも声を出してほしいな！
For the next song, I'd love for everyone to cheer along!
一緒に最後まで楽しもうね！
Let's enjoy it together until the end!
ラプくんも！
You too, Rapu-kun!
はっ！もちろんです！もう声枯れるまでやります！
Ah! Of course! I'll cheer until I lose my voice!
ふふ、ラプくん、喉は大事にしてね！
Hehe, Rapu-kun, make sure to take care of your throat!
あ、あの！李波お姉さん！
Ah, um! Ribo-oneesan!
我が輩の先輩もどうしてもライブ見たいって言ってるんですけど、呼んでいいですか？
My senior says she really wants to see the concert too, is it okay if I invite her?
ふふ、誰誰ー？ぜひー！
Hehe, who is it? Please, by all means!
すみませ〜ん！お邪魔しま〜す！
Excuse me~! Sorry to intrude~!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
It's a pleasure to meet you!
さくらみこさん、お会いできて光栄です！
Sakura Miko-san, it's an honor to meet you!
こ、こちらこそです！パフォーマンス楽しみにしてます！
Th-The honor is all mine! I'm really looking forward to your performance!
ふふっ、お姉さん、頑張っちゃうよ！
Hehe, this big sister is going to do her best!
か、可愛すぎる...
C-Too cute...
それでは、次の曲、聴いてください！
Now then, please listen to the next song!
回想中 熱くなり お茶いかが？
Reminiscing, getting heated up... how about some tea?
冷静に大人で ハートは君に
Cool and mature, but my heart belongs to you.
まだ教えずに ご相談 チラチラと
Without telling you yet, asking for advice while stealing glances.
余裕 身に着けて 言う「お相手はyou？」
Putting on a composed act, asking, "Is your partner you?"
ドラマのようなことしない 女優
An actress who doesn't do dramatic things.
噛めば噛むほど美味しい lady
A lady who gets more delightful the more you know her.
例に甘え方を見せてほしい
I want you to show me how to lean on you.
一緒に歌ってくれる？
Will you sing along with me?
はみ出したい〜 変われないの
I want to break free~ but I can't change.
自由型のいい子は好き放題
The freestyle good girl does as she pleases.
その塩梅〜 わからないの
That sweet spot... I don't know it.
優しいふりして ただ焦ってる
Pretending to be gentle, but secretly flustered.
ふたりとも良く出来ました！
You two did great!
ちょっと... ラプくん！
Wait... Rapu-kun!
そっと焦らして 君を
Tantalizing you softly,
見つめ合おう
let's gaze at each other.
そっと心タップ 君を
Gently tapping into your heart,
あぁ 君を知りたい
ah, I want to know you.
ラストもお願い！
Give it your all for the last part too!
はみ出したい〜 変われないの
I want to break free~ but I can't change.
自由型のいい子は好き放題
The freestyle good girl does as she pleases.
その塩梅〜 わからないの
That sweet spot... I don't know it.
優しいふりして ただ焦ってる
Pretending to be gentle, but secretly flustered.
もっと！
More!
慌てないの 誰だってリードしたいけど
Don't panic, anyone would want to take the lead, but...
そのボーダー 越えられないの
I can't cross that border.
そもそもの話 まだ確認して
In the first place, still making sure...
見つめている
I'm staring at you...
「clumsy trick」でした！
That was "clumsy trick"!
どうだったかな？
How was it?
最高でした！ 最高です！
It was the best! The absolute best!
ラプ君とあんな風に一緒にパフォーマンスすることになるなんて
I never expected to perform together with Lap-kun like that...
楽しかったな～
It was so much fun~
よかったらこっちで一緒に話そうよ
If you'd like, come talk over here with me.
いやいやいや…ここが、ここがやっぱり落ち着くんですけれど…
No, no, no... It's just that I feel much more comfortable right here...
さっきは一緒にステージにいてくれたのに？
Even though you were on stage with me just earlier?
行っておいでよ！ 呼ばれてるんだから！
Go on over! She's calling for you!
え、今行きます！ 待っててください！
Eh, I'm coming right now! Please wait for me!
急に出てくるからびっくりしちゃったよ
You appeared so suddenly that you surprised me!
申し訳ありません、なんか…もう我慢できなくて
I'm so sorry, I just... couldn't hold back anymore.
そんな破天荒なところがラプ君の魅力だよね
That wild, unpredictable side is your charm, Lap-kun.
私も見習いたいよ
I want to learn from you too.
え、いや！ もうリナミお姉さんはこのままで素敵です！
Eh, no! Rinami-onesan is already wonderful just as you are!
そのままでいてください！
Please stay just the way you are!
ありがとう
Thank you.
これからもお互い、アイドルとして頑張ろうね
Let's both keep doing our best as idols from now on.
恐縮です！ もうありがとうございます！ 頑張ります！
I'm so honored! Thank you so much! I'll do my best!
またこうやって一緒に共演できたら嬉しいな
I'd be so happy if we could perform together like this again.
それも…もう恐縮です！ ありがとうございます！
That too... I'm so deeply honored! Thank you so much!
今日はありがとう！
Thank you for today!
とっても素敵なミニライブでした！
It was a truly wonderful mini live!
みんなも楽しんでくれたかな？
Did everyone enjoy it too?
それじゃあ、またね！
Well then, see you later!
ラプ君も！
You too, Lap-kun!
えっ、リナミお姉さん！
Eh, Rinami-onesan?!
お姉さんー！
Onesan—!